jerusalem.com 2013-05-24

# Privacy Policy - Jerusalem

This Privacy Policy explains how Jerusalem.com collects and uses data. If not otherwise defined herein, capitalized terms have the meaning given to them in the Jerusalem.com Terms of Use, which is available at <http://jerusalem.com/terms> (the “ **Terms** ”).

Jerusalem.com Guide Ltd respects your right to privacy. Your ability to make informed choices about the uses of your information is important to us. This Privacy Policy explains Jerusalem.com’s policy regarding the collection, use, disclosure and protection of any information we receive. 

## Information We Collect 

In order to use our Site and some of our Services, you may be required to register and provide us with certain Personal Information. We also collect Personal Information when you make use of the Services, such as booking a hotel room, or contact us for any other reason. “ **Personal Information** ” means information that can be directly associated with a specific person or entity such as a name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card number and expiration date, or information about activities directly linked to a person, such as that person’s location. Examples of the Personal Information that we collect from you include your name, location and e-mail address. You may register through your Facebook account and may choose to log in through the Facebook Connect Feature, Twitter or Google Plus. By doing so, you are asking those entities to send us certain information from your profile and authorize us to collect, store and use this information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. It is your voluntary decision whether to provide us with any such Personal Information, but if you refuse to provide such information we may not be able to register you or allow certain uses of the Site and/or Services.

You may provide information on behalf of another entity.  If you completed the registration or provide information on behalf of a certain entity, you represent to us that you were authorized by that entity to give us consent to use the submitted information.

Customer Testimonials.  We may post customer testimonials on the site, which may contain personal information.  We do obtain the customers’ consent via e-mail prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial.  To request removal of your personal information from our testimonials, contact us at <info@jerusalem.com>.  In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

In addition, when you use Jerusalem.com certain non personally identifiable information may be automatically gathered about your IP address, geolocation information, mobile device, browser type, browser language or operating system. We may use third party contractors to collect and aggregate this information.   For more information, please see Cookies and other technologies.

## How we Protect Information

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security **.**

When you enter sensitive information such as credit card number on our order form, our merchant services providers encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We will delete any information provided to us by a user upon the receipt of a written request by such user. We cannot restore information that we have deleted.

## How we Use Information 

We and our affiliates may use personal information provided to us to as follows:

  * To enable us to verify your credentials, in order to maintain reasonable security, provide developers with the information that is useful in developing new features and services for our users, allow us to potentially vary advertising based on user preference, usage preferences and demographics, enable us to develop and improve the features, contents, and services available,  fulfill your requests for our Services, in connection with your use of the Site or Services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, to offer you our products or services that we believe may be of interest to you, to carry out transactions which you have requested, to enforce our rights and resolve disputes. 
  * We will retain information transmitted to us in the context of use of Services for further internal use in connection with our efforts to improve our Services and products.
  * We may use non-personally identifying information that we collect to provide statistical information about users of the Site or Services, to improve the quality, design and content of our Site, to analyze the use of our Site and to cooperate with law enforcement.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

Except as expressly set forth herein, we will not share, rent or trade your Personal Information with third parties without your explicit permission. 

  * We may use Personal Information internally – for example, to help diagnose problems with our servers, to make Jerusalem.com more useful, to customize Jerusalem.com and personalize its content for you.
  * Third-party vendors who provide services to us or facilitate or evaluate the Sites or Services, such as e-mail service providers sending e-mails on our behalf.      We may also authorize third-party vendors or service providers to collect information on our behalf. 
  * Business partners with whom we may jointly offer products or services, or whose products or services may be offered on our website or together with our software. You can tell when a third party is involved in a product or service because their name will appear, either alone or with ours. If you choose to use these products or services, we may share information about you, including your personal information, with those partners. Please note that we do not control the privacy practices of these third-party business partners.  If you wish to no longer allow that third party to use your information you may opt-out by contacting that third party directly. 
  * In addition, by analyzing all information we receive, including all information concerning users and hotel (or other Services) bookings, we may compile statistical information across a variety of users (“ **Statistical Information** ”). Statistical Information helps understand trends and customer needs so that new products and services can be considered and so existing products and services can be tailored to customer desires. Statistical Information is anonymous and we will not link Statistical Information to any Personal Information. We may share Statistical Information with our partners, without restriction, on commercial terms that we can determine in our sole discretion. We also use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about the use of the Site and/or Services. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this Site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this Site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve our Site and Services. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html) located at  <http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html> and the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html) located at http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ Please see the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy for additional information. 
  * Referring websites.  If you were referred to this website from another site (for example, through a link you clicked on another site that directed you to this one), we may share some information about you with that referring website. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any website that referred you here. 
  * Companies within our corporate family that are involved in operating or providing the Services. We may share your personal information with our affiliates.  Our affiliates will follow practices that are at least as restrictive as the practices described in this Privacy Policy, including requests that personal information not be used to provide you with Services. 
  * The advertisements you see on this website are served by us or by our service providers. But we also allow third parties to collect information about your online activities through cookies and other technologies. These third parties include (1) business partners, who collect information when you interact with one of their advertisements on our site; and (2) advertising networks, which collect information about your interests when you interact with one of the advertisements they place on various websites on the Internet. The information gathered by these third parties is used to make predictions about your interests or preferences and to display advertisements on our sites and across the Internet tailored to your apparent interests. We do not permit these third parties to collect personal information about you (such as email address) on our site, nor do we share with them any personal information about you. 
  * Please note that we do not have access to or control over cookies or other technologies these third parties may use to collect information about your interests, and the information practices of these third parties are not covered by this Privacy Policy

We may share aggregated or anonymous data with third parties for any use whatsoever. 

We also may share your information:

  * In response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process or in response to a law enforcement agency’s request; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases we reserve the right to raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us. 
  * When we believe it is appropriate to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal or suspected illegal activities; to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of our company or this website, our customers, or others; and in connection with our Terms and Conditions for the Site, and other agreements. 
  * In the event that InternetDominion.com or Jerusalem.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred.  You will be notified via email or prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 
  * Other than as set out above, you will be notified when personal information about you will be shared with third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to have us share such information.  Jerusalem.com does not sell, rent or lease the personal information that you provide about yourself to third parties unless we have your consent. 

## Google Maps

We use Google Maps on our Site. Use of Google Maps is subject to the Google privacy policy, available at <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>.  

## Feedback

When you post Content on Jerusalem.com, please remember that any information disclosed in this venue may be automatically made public, and such information will not be considered Personal Information by Jerusalem.com. You should exercise caution when disclosing any information (including Personal Information) in such a venue, as you do not know who will access or use such information and for what purposes.

## Cookies 

A cookie is a small piece of text that is sent to a visitor's browser. The browser provides this piece of text to the device of the originating visitor when this visitor returns. Jerusalem.com uses cookies to help personalize your Jerusalem.com experience. A “persistent” cookie may be used to help save your settings and customizations across site visits. Also, if you log in to Jerusalem.com, such a cookie will be used to recognize you as a valid user so you will not need to log in each time you use Jerusalem.com. Most Web browsers are initially configured to accept cookies, but you can change this setting so your browser either refuses all cookies or informs you when a cookie is being sent. Also, you are free to delete any existing cookies at any time. Please note that some features of Jerusalem.com may not function properly when cookies are disabled or removed.

## Third Parties and Online Links to Other Sites 

Jerusalem.com members or users can link to other websites of third-parties that provide useful information/services. Any personal information you provide on the linked pages is provided directly to this third-party and is subject to that third-party’s provider’s privacy policy. Additionally, when you book a hotel through our partner Expedia, you share your Personal Information directly with Expedia and Expedia’s privacy policy governs the collection and use of this information. We do not have access to the information collected by Expedia.Except as described above, Jerusalem.com is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of Expedia and the other Web sites to which we link. Links from our site to third-parties or other sites are provided for your convenience. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of each web site before providing them with personal information. We cannot be held responsible for any third-party Web sites and accessing their content will be subject to their own privacy policies, which again - we advise you to check.

## Correcting or Updating your Information

Jerusalem.com allows you to view the information you provided during registration and to alter any data, inaccuracies or errors. To request such access, or correct, update, or amend your personal information please contact us at the following e-mail address: 

E-mail address: <http://jerusalem.com/terms>

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services.  If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, please contact us at the e-mail address, postal address, or telephone number listed above.  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

## Communications

We may send you email messages about us or our products and services as well as email messages about products and services of selected third parties. By accepting the Terms and Conditions for the Site (including the terms of this Privacy Policy which are incorporated therein) or using the Site or the Services, you affirmatively consent to receive such commercial messages.  As a registered member, you can remove your personal information from our mailing list and to stop receiving future communication from us by following the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each communication or by emailing us at <info@jerusalem.com>. You will also be given the opportunity to unsubscribe from commercial messages in any such email we send.  Please note that we reserve the right to send you service related communications, including service announcements and administrative messages, relating either to your account or to your transactions on this site, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them unless you cancel your account. 

## Use of Jerusalem.com by Children

Jerusalem.com does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. In the event you become aware that an individual under the age of 13 has enrolled without parental permission, please advise us immediately.

Games: we may provide games on our Site. In order to fully enjoy this Service, we may ask children to register and provide us with certain information, such as an email and a password. In order to register, we will require the consent of a parent and/or guardian.

## Other Uses or Transfer of Your Information

We will fully cooperate with any law enforcement authorities or court order requesting or directing us to disclose the identity, behavior or digital content of any user suspected to have engaged in illegal or infringing behavior. 

In providing the Services, we may use subcontractors that are located in countries other than your own, and send them information we receive. For example, we may send your information to any countries outside your home country. All our subcontractors will be subject to non-disclosure and non-use obligations. Nevertheless, some countries may have levels of protection of personal and other information which are not as high as in your country of residence or business. By providing personal information or using our Site or Services, you consent to transfer of information outside your country in connection with the transfers of information described in this Privacy Policy, even to countries that might not offer a level of protection for your personal information that is equivalent to the one offered in your country of residence.

We may transfer our databases containing your Personal Information if we sell our business or part of it. 

## Changes

Jerusalem.com may update this Privacy Policy from time to time - we encourage you to review it periodically.

## Comments and Questions

If you have any comments or questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at [info@jerusalem.com]
